{
    "id": "6e63fe2a4162423daca030f2588be2a8",
    "title": "Verb + prepositions exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0c41958aad844b84a012b590d21140a0",
            "title": "Verb + Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why are you looking ………………… me like that?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like you to listen ………………….. this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let us talk ………………… your new projects.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "about",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ran ………………… James at Victoria Station yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "into",
                        "at",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long have you been married ………………… her?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am thinking ………………….. studying engineering.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "of",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A week after the accident he died ………………… his injuries.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "with",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I half believe …………………. life after death.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I must apologize ............................... disturbing you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "about",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He left the firm because he didn’t agree ................................... their sales policy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}